{
    "id": "kennypain",
    "name": "Kenny Pain",
    "yomi": "ケニーペイン",
    "text": [
        "1996年生まれ大阪在住",
        "born in Osaka, 1996"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/k_e_n_n_y_p_a_i_n/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Are you an only child?",
            "jp": "貴方は1人っ子？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Can you sleep without a pillow?",
            "jp": "枕が無くても寝れる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "You listen to music with",
            "jp": "音楽を聴くときは？",
            "yes": "an earphone",
            "left": "イヤホン",
            "no": "a headphone",
            "right": "ヘッドホン"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "When you sleep you turn the light",
            "jp": "寝るときの電気は？",
            "yes": "Off",
            "left": "消す",
            "no": "On",
            "right": "消さない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Do you think human beings were born from soil?",
            "jp": "人間は土から生まれたと思う？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "思う",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "思わない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "If you should cut either cord which color would you choose?",
            "jp": "コードを切るなら？",
            "yes": "red",
            "left": "赤",
            "no": "blue",
            "right": "青"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Weather tomorrow?",
            "jp": "あ〜した天気にな〜れ？",
            "yes": "sunny",
            "left": "晴れ",
            "no": "rainy or cloudy",
            "right": "雨・くもり"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you believe fortune-telling by blood type?",
            "jp": "血液型性格診断は？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "信じる",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "信じない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you want to live near a riverbed?",
            "jp": "河川敷近くのアパートに？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "住みたい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "住みたくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Are you dreaming now?",
            "jp": "いま夢をみている？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        }
    ]
}